<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patiala</string>
    <string name="description"><b>Located in the culturally rich state of Punjab, Patiala is a historic city resplendent with architectural marvels and cultural heritage of the yore.</b> The people here are large hearted, affable and extremely warm and it is highly recommended to experience the hospitality of the place.The city is situated near Qila Mubarak which was constructed in the year 1763 bya militiaman, Baba Ala Singh. Patiala is very well known for its traditional turban, Patiala Salwar, Paranda, Jutti and Patiala Peg.Patiala travel guide is incomplete without a mention of its rich heritage.<b>Rakesh Sharma</b>, the first Indian astronaut was born in Patiala.The city is also accredited as the “City of Newspapers”.The popular printing press of Nawal Kishore was founded in the 19th century in Patiala. Being the home of Hindustani classical music, it is also renowned as Patiala Gharana.Patiala has also emerged as a major educational center of Punjab after freedom and comprises of several first class institutes.It is also the home to some popular personalities of India like Jimmy Shergil, Om Puri, Navjot Singh Sidhu, Mohinder Amarnath, Naresh Goyal and Harbhajan Mann.Since ages, Patiala has been the center of various types of trades and still the same tradition continues. One who comes to Patiala would never be able to resist the temptation to buy various types of items from Patiala. Patiala has some old traditional market places as well as the modernized ones keeping in mind the likings of the modern buyers.\nThe best season to visit Patiala is the winter season.The temperature remains comfortable and is apt for sightseeing.The best months to visit are October, November, December, January, and February.</string>
    <string name="guru">This Sikh shrine is located in the small village of Lehal which is now a part of Patiala city.</string>
    <string name="qilamubarak">This a Historical National Monument of Patiala is situated in the heart of the city and the oldest part of Patiala.</string>
    <string name="sheesh">The Sheesh Mahal is the famous tourist place in Patiala. Maharaja Narinder Singh built this Mahal in 1847.</string>
    <string name="baradari">The importance Baradari garden can be ascertained from its name. This name was formed with two words of Punjabi Bara and Dar.</string>
    <string name="kali_mandir">One of the consecrated place of worship for the Hindus, the Kali Devi Temple in the city of Patiala in the Indian state of Punjab.</string>
    <string name="moti">With 15 dining halls, the massive Moti Bagh Palace was counted amongst one of the largest residences in Asia.</string>
    <string name="nis">Netaji Subhas National Institute of Sports is the largest sports institute of Asia and is popularly known as NIS Patiala.</string>

    <string name="adalat">Adalat Bazar Patiala is one exciting place for sightseeing because of its vibrant milieu.</string>
    <string name="qila">If you are in search of a market that has a colorful atmosphere with all sorts of traditional and stylish accessories, then must visit this market.</string>
    <string name="omaxe">Spread over a staggering 3.55 lakh square feet with 2.3 lakh square feet of operational space,adds on to the beauty, viability and desirability of Omaxe Mall.</string>
    <string name="ac">AC Market is fully air conditioned. This awe-inspiring completely air-conditioned shopping heaven is spread crosswise four storeys and boasts of over 650 shops.</string>
    <string name="phul">Visit the Phulkari Emporium to shop for a broad range of suits that are made using this unique embroidery technique.</string>
    <string name="dharam">Dharampura Market might not be that big, but this section of Patiala is known for offering high-end electronic goods.</string>
    <string name="gurun">Gurudwara Dukhniwaran Sahib</string>
    <string name="qilan">Qila Mubarak</string>
    <string name="sheeshn">Sheesh Mahal</string>
    <string name="baran">Baradari</string>
    <string name="kalin">Kali Mandir</string>
    <string name="motin">Moti Bagh Palace</string>
    <string name="netan">Netaji Subhas National Institute of Sports</string>
    <string name="neemn">Neemrana\'s Baradari Hotel</string>
    <string name="mohann">Hotel Mohan Continental</string>
    <string name="harbans">Hotel Harbans Residency</string>
    <string name="eqbaln">Eqbal Inn</string>
    <string name="amarn">Amar Hotel</string>
    <string name="godn">Godwin</string>
    <string name="ajuban">Hotel Ajuba Mehbooba</string>
    <string name="jailn">Food Jail</string>
    <string name="baristan">Barsita</string>
    <string name="brewn">Brew Estate</string>
    <string name="gopaln">Gopal\'s</string>
    <string name="bostonn">Boston Bites</string>
    <string name="yellown">Yellow Chillies</string>
    <string name="ccdn">CCD</string>

    <string name="adalatn">Adalat Bazar</string>
    <string name="qilann">Qila Mubarak</string>
    <string name="omaxen">Omaxe Mall</string>
    <string name="acn">AC Market</string>
    <string name="phulkarin">Phulkari Punjab Govt Emporium</string>
    <string name="dharamn">Dharampura Bazaar</string>









</resources>
